https://www.teamnames.net/privacy-policy

Team Names by Genre
AmusingAnimalBaseballBeer PongBowlingBusinessCleverCoolCorporateCreativeCricketDodgeballDrinkingFantasy BaseballFantasy BasketballFantasy FootballFantasy HockeyFlag FootballFoodFootballFunFunnyGamingGirlsGolfGoodHockeyKickballNascarOlympicPaintballPubQuizRacingRugbyRunningSchoolSillySoccerSoftballSportTennisTriviaVolleyballWalkingWeight LossWeirdWorkWrestling
Games
Team Name Hangman
Name That Stadium
Other
Stadium Name Generator
Team Name of the Week
Twitter
Facebook
© 2006 - 2020 TeamNames.net - All rights reserved
Home
Privacy & Cookie Policy
Privacy & Cookie Policy
This privacy policy sets out how TeamNames.net uses and protects any information that you give TeamNames.net when you use this website.
TeamNames.net is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
TeamNames.net may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
Your access and usage of TeamNames.net ("we", "us", or "the website") is subject to the following Privacy and Cookie Policy, Terms & Conditions of Use and all other applicable laws.
Data Collection
We will never collect personally identifiable information without your prior consent, such as you registering an account with the website.
By registering and creating an account with the website, you permit the storage of your personal details and any other data required to provide the service. As a result of registering and logging into your account, you permit the collection of data such as, but not limited to, your name, job title, contact information including email address, demographic information such as location, other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers, website searches and browsing trends that will individually identify you. All data is stored securely on servers and is not accessible by the general public.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. We will only use your details for marketing purposes should you opt-in during the data collection process.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. Further information on the operation of cookies is available from AboutCookies.org.
The following details the cookies that are used throughout the website, along with any third-parties that are used.
First Party Cookies
Cookie Name
Purpose
sess
This cookie is set when visiting the website, and is used on a per session basis. It is used to provide core functionality to the website, such as website forms, account login sessions, and team name voting.
geo
This cookie is used to store a visitor's geographic location, in order to enhance functionality of the website to provide visitors with more relevant content.
lay
This cookie is used to test and optimize web page layouts to help improve the visitor experience.
tnhangman
This cookie is used to provide scoring functionality to our Hangman game.
tntoollist
This cookie is used to store your favorite team names. Team names are added to your short list by browsing the website, and clicking the relevant "Add" buttons.
tn_auto
This cookie is used to automatically log you into a registered user account. This allows visitors to use the website without having to login to their account each time. This is an optional preference, set when a visitor logs into their account.
Google Analytics Cookies
Cookie Name
Purpose
__utma, __utmb, __utmc, __utmz
These cookies enable the function of Google Analytics. This software helps us take and analyze visitor information such as browser usage, new visitor numbers, and visitor locations. This information helps us to improve the website and your user experience, and to make our marketing efforts relevant.
The data stored by these cookies can be seen only by the relevant teams at TeamNames.net and Google, and never shows any confidential information.
The Google Analytics implementation on this website has been enabled to support and record data for the purpose of Google Analyics Demographic and Interest Reporting. Visitors are able to opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising by using the Ads Settings. Visitors may also visit Google Analyics' currently available opt-outs.
The data from Google's Interest-based advertising, or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests), is used for the purpose of understanding the type of user that interacts with the website.
This allows us to understand the user demographics much better, allowing us to cater for the user better, with the aim of improving the end user experience.
YouTube Cookies
Cookie Name
Purpose
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE, use_hitbox, PREF, GEO
These cookies are set by YouTube. We use YouTube to embed video content throughout the website to enhance the user experience. Should you require further information, you may read YouTube and Google's Privacy Policy.
Sharing Tools & Cookies
Platform Name
Purpose
Facebook
We use Facebook Social Plugins and sharing tools to allow visitors to share content. Examples of Facebook sharing tools include the "Like" button, "Send" button, and "Like" box. We do not control the setting of Facebook cookies, so please check the Facebook Privacy Policy for further information.
Twitter
We use Twitter Buttons and sharing tools to allow visitors to share content. Examples of Twitter sharing tools include the "Tweet" and "Follow" buttons. We do not control the setting of Twitter cookies, so please check the Twitter Privacy Policy for further information.
Google+
We use Google+ Buttons and sharing tools to allow visitors to share content. Examples of Google+ sharing tools include the "+1" button. We do not control the setting of Google+ cookies, so please check the Google Privacy Policy for further information.
AddThis
We use AddThis Buttons and sharing tools to allow visitors to share content. Examples of AddThis sharing tools include the "Share" button. We do not control the setting of AddThis cookies, so please check the AddThis Privacy Policy for further information.
Third-Party Advertising Cookies
When you visit TeamNames.net, you may notice that some of the cookies aren't related or set by the TeamNames.net website.
When you visit a web page that contains embedded content, such as banner advertising, you may be sent cookies from a third party website. We don't control the setting of these cookies, so we strongly recommend that you check the third party websites for further information about their cookies, usage, and how to manage them.
You should note that:
Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this website.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to this website.
You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page. (Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.)
Listed below are some examples of third-party advertisers that may set cookies as a direct result of you visiting the TeamNames.net website. Google provide a complete list of third-party advertising vendors.
DoubleClick
Google
Chitika
Invite Media
Specific Click
MediaPlex
eBay
Media Innovation Group
Other Third-Party Relationships
On occasion, we may collaborate with third parties in order to complete tasks such as, but not limited to, updating the website, executing campaigns, and improving the website service. We will never share any personal information about yourself with any third party unless required by legal or regulatory obligation. The website adheres to the Data Protection Act of 1998 accordingly, and if at any point you wish to gain access to any information that we store about yourself, then you may do so by completing the form on our contact page. A small fee will be payable for the request.
Opt-Out From Further Messages or Communications
If you have previously opted-in to receive further communications from us, then you can opt-out of such messages by logging into your account and un-subscribing from the service. Should you experience any issues with un-subscribing then you can contact us.
